point here is that he was not eating the
right foods outwardly he looked
fit and healthy but internally he was
eating food or
putting something in his body that was
accelerating the asian process and
promoting tissue damage
to his arteries okay and so what i
want to do is show
show you guys something
can you hear us yeah dr reynolds can you
hear us
okay can you repeat you were breaking up
a little bit
when you were talking about what the
pathologist said
um can you repeat
what he said when you looked at the
heart when he looked at the heart
or the arteries yeah he said that
the the way the arteries appear then
the arteries looked like that of a 60
year old man
right you did say that and what did he
say he should have been eating or
he said without eating he was the reason
his arteries
looked as bad as they they did was
because he
was consuming he had a dietary
practice that was causing the arteries
to
to look aged the way they were right and
i i
couldn't believe that so i asked him
could there have been something
else to cause that and he said no
this this is not if it were drug related
which is other reasons why the heart
will be damaged
it would appear to look one way and
he said no that's not what it is this is
he he was just
really um eating the wrong stuff
and i was shocked because at the time i
didn't really
know that who would have that severe of
an impact
on on the structure of the heart and the
arteries so
it really hit me there we go okay yeah
we can see that wow
okay question we see this picture
you guys tell me what do you guys think
this
is type one for
hamburger or two you don't know
that's clearly a hamburger i say it's a
hamburger
or two okay i don't know you're just
saying we lead a congregation too
so everybody just go ahead and put one
because no
it's i think we all know that that is
clearly a hamburger
uh something okay i'm not very happy to
hear it
so i'm sad to tell you guys that this
is a beyond meat patty plant-based oh
beyond meatbag
i thought it looked like that too i was
gonna say that actually
oh i remember this is a beyond meat
patty
and it's plant-based you guys saw the
oil
did you those are hydrogen that's
hydrogenated oil trans fat
that's when you consume it goes off and
promote
damage to your arteries a damage to all
of your tissues
so you don't want to eat things like
that that is not food
that's damaging you just broke my heart
did she hear me you just broke my heart
because i eat those
and you know and this is why you and i
like
these eaters dying from the same
diseases you know as meat eaters because
of things like that it's it we need to
eat whole
foods